Previously on "desperate housewives"...
(前情提要)
the police dug upyour father today.
警察今天把你爸爸的尸体挖出来了
They think that somebodywas poisoning him.
他们怀疑有人给他下毒
Apparently,I'm a suspect.
显而易见 我是嫌疑犯
Bree felt threatened by the past.
(往事给Bree带来威胁）
- Get the damn lawyer. - Are you hitting on me?
你是在挑逗我么
Gabrielle was threatened by seduction.
(而Gabrielle的威胁来自诱惑）
Do you mean julie?
你是说Julie?
If I come back with you,then I can make it up to her.
我跟你回去 我就能弥补她了
You should find your fatherfirst. Let me help.
你应该先找你的爸爸 我帮你
And while some threats...
(一些威胁)
Were kept under control...
(尽在掌握）
let's get this over with.
你动手吧
Some were left free to return.
(而另一些) (却成为后患）
Since her first day on the job,
(自从第一天上班）
it had been clear to lynette scavo
(Lynette Scavo就已经清楚）
that her new boss nina was unusually tense.
(她的新老板Nina 神经过分紧张）
To help relieve her tension,
(为了帮她缓解）
lynette tried giving her boss thoughtful gifts--
(Lynette尝试过送老板心意十足的礼物）
a soothing wave machine...
(缓解压力的波浪机）
aromatherapy candles...
(熏香蜡烛）
even meditative chi balls.
(甚至太极健身球）
But nothing seemed to ease nina's tension.
(但似乎没有什么能让Nina放松下来）
"Distilledthe old-fashioned way."
"蒸馏传统"?
You know,it actually hurts my teeth
知道么 我大声读出来都会伤到牙
to say that out loud.
You folks are going to toddleback to your little holes
你们几个给我爬回各自的窝儿
and you are gonna come upwith a decent slogan
想出一个得体的标语
or I will can all your assesthe old-fashioned way.
不然我就按"传统"不开你们的薪
Until one day when it occurred to lynette
(终于有一天） (Lynette才想到）
there was one form of relaxation
(还有一种放松的方法她没尝试）
she had yet to try.
It's a gimlet.You'll love it.
这酒叫螺丝钻 你肯定喜欢
What exactlyis your plan here,
你到底想干什么 把我灌醉了让我同意你的修订方案？
to get me all liquored upso I buy the revised pitch?
Don't be ridiculous.
别逗了
Could we get a trough
能给我们来一槽子这种酒么
of these,please?
I can't remember the last timeI was in a bar.
都不记得我上次泡酒吧是什么时候了
Must have been the last timeI had a boyfriend,
应该是我和最后一个男友在一起时
which was...
那就应该是
oh,god,I'm a nun.
天哪 我都成修女了
So why don't you go outand get in the game?
那你干嘛不找一个呢
Believe it or not,
信不信由你
when it comes to meeting men,I am... shy.
跟男人搭讪我总是
Well,I'm not.
我不害羞阿
So,uh...
那么
what about that guyover there?
那边那个人怎么样
He's been checking you outsince we walked in.
我们一进来他就一直瞄着你
He's cute.
挺帅
So go over there.
那就过去阿
no.
- 不去
Oh,for god's sakes.
- 哦 你可真是
Where are you going?Lynette,sit--
你干嘛去 Lynette 坐
hey,stretch,
嗨 帅哥
see my friend over there?
看见我那边的朋友了么 她觉得你很帅
She thinks you're cute.
她觉得你很帅
Why don't youbuy her a drink?
请她喝一杯吧
Hey,everybody. Hi.
嗨 大伙 早
Oh,it's a beautiful morning,isn't it?
哦 早晨的天气不错是吧
Thank you,sweetie.
谢谢 甜心
Oh,hey,lynette,I readthe new vodka proposal.
我看了伏特加新的策划
Oh,you guys hit itout of the park.
哦 可真有你们的
I love that color.
- 颜色真漂亮
Thanks.
谢谢
Hey,nina.
喂 Nina
Yeah?
干嘛
And although it had come about in an unexpected manner...
(虽然结果是Nina举止出人意料）
aren't those the same clothes you were wearing last nightin the bar?
这套衣服是不是你昨晚酒吧里那套？
Yep.
对极了
Nina's tension had finally been released...
(她的紧张情绪终于被 最"传统"的方法缓解了)
the old-fashioned way.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=- Proudly Presents
-=伊甸园论坛 http://wwwydycom=- 荣誉出品 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
Everyone in this world
(世上的每一个人都需要有人依靠）
needs someone they can depend upon,
be it a faithful companion,
(一个可靠的陪护）
trusted confidant...
(信赖的知己）
or loyal friend.
(或者忠诚的朋友）
For susan mayer,that dependable someone
(对Susan Mayer来说）
was her book agent lonny moon.
(就是她的出版经纪人 Lonny Moon)
It was lonny
(是Lonny帮susan出版她第一本儿童读物)
who helped susan promote her first children's book.
It was lonny who rushed susan to the hospital
(是Lonny在Julie出生 那晚送Susan去医院）
the night julie was born.
It was lonny who took susan's mind
(是Lonny带Susan旅行散心 让她忘掉痛苦的离婚）
off her painful divorce
with a fun vacation.
(是Lonny带Susan旅行散心 让她忘掉痛苦的离婚）
Yes,lonny was susan's rock.
(是啊 Lonny是Susan的支柱）
Sadly for susan,
(但susan真是不幸）
her rock was about to crumble.
(她的支柱就要倒了）
for those of you just joining us,
刚刚转过台的观众 melanie Foster的案子有了新的进展
we have a new development in the melanie foster case...
lonny,what are you doing here?
- Lonny 你怎么来了
It's past noon.
- 中午过了
Which means it's now socially acceptable
这说明喝酒已经符合社交礼仪了
to begin drinking.
I can't believe I let youtalk me into this.
我怎么就被你劝服了呢 我的进度已经落后了
I am so behind in my work.
But I'm glad I came.This is fun.
但还是很高兴我来了 我很开心
I've gotta be honest.
跟你实话实说
I had an ulterior motive.
- 我是有求而来
Oh?
哦？
I've decided to start my own agency.
我决定开办自己的公司
You're leaving muir and hunt?
你要离开Muir&Hunt?
You helped build that place.
那儿是你一手操办起来的
I know,but I just feelit's time.
我知道 但我想是时候了
And now the question is,will you come with me?
现在的问题是 你要来我这边么
Well... of course.
唔当然
Okay!
好！
To the future.
为未来干杯
I'll just call the agency,
我要给公司打个电话 告诉他们我跟你干了
and I'll let them knowI'm going with you.
Oh,I don't thinkthat's necessary.
这没有必要
Really?
是么？
Yeah,I thinkit might be rude not to.
要是不的话太没礼貌了
Lonny...
Lonny 到底怎么了
what's going on?
Okay.
好吧
There's been some bad bloodbetween me and the partners.
我和公司其他人搞得很僵
Why?
为什么
I got into this thingwhere I had to move
我把客户的钱临时挪用到别的花销上了
a little client moneyaround temporarily
to cover some expenses.
我把客户的钱临时挪用到别的花销上了
You had to "move money"?What does that mean?
你挪用钱了？什么意思
I took a little from here,and I moved it there.
我从这拿一些 添到别的账上
It was no big deal.
- 没什么大不了的
Really?
是么？
'Cause it sort of soundslike embezzlement.
- 听起来似乎是盗用公款
Why do peoplekeep using that word?!
怎么你们都这么说
Who else is usingthat word?
- 还谁这么说了
Nobody.
没人
The partners and their forensic accountant.
同事还有法庭的会计他们
Oh,my god.
哦 天哪
Lonny,did you "move"some of my money?
Lonny 你挪用过我的钱么
Absolutely not.I swear!
绝对没有 我发誓
Susan,don't look at methat way.
Susan 别这么看着我
I know what I didwas wrong,
我知道我做得不对
and I feel likea complete idiot for doing it,
我觉得自己很愚蠢
but please,please don't hate me.
但求求你 求求你不要恨我
Well,I don't hate you.
我不恨你 我不会恨你的 你是我的Lonny
I couldn't hate you.You're my lonny.
So...
那
will you stillcome with me?
你还到我那工作么
This is one of those times
这是考验谁是真朋友的时候
when you find outwho your real friends are,
so,yeah.
所以我答应你
Oh,thank you!Thank you!
哦 谢谢 谢谢
You are one special lady,susan mayer.
你是位特别的女士 Susan Mayer
Is that the baby's head?
- 这是孩子的头么
No,that's his foot.
- 不 这是脚
That looks like a head to me.
我看着像脚
Well,that settles it.
那就说定了
When this baby's born,
孩子出生以后 我负责给他穿袜子
I'll be in chargeof putting on the socks.
You're glowing today,you know that?
你今天美极了 你知道么
Pregnancy agrees with you.
- 你怀孕时候很美
Yeah?
是么
Well,if you don't mind the hemorrhoids and the nausea,
你要是不算上痔疮和呕吐
it's quite the party.
怀孕倒的确不错
So this new lawyer's good?
- 新的律师还不错？
He's quite the shark. You're gonna love him.
- 是个狠手 你肯定满意
He hasn't lost a casein six years.
6年他没输过一桩案子
He argued in front of the state supreme court,
他在州最高法院辩护过
and he made our conjugal visithappen pretty damn fast.
我们的配偶探访他办的特她妈快
Well,hey,I'm a fan already.
哦 我已经对他着迷了 对不起我来晚了
Sorry I'm late.
对不起我来晚了
Oh,david.
哦 David
Good to see you,gaby.Carlos,I'm david.
很高兴见到你 Gaby Carlos 我是David
I don't think so.
我不要他
What the hellare you doing?
你要干什么
That guy's not gonna bemy lawyer.
我不要他当我律师
Find a new one.
找个新的
You haven't fileda single charge.
你一项指控都没有
Either determine a homicideor release the body.
要么确认是他杀 要么还回尸体
We've got a court orderwhich says,
法律上说明 知道我们结束案子 死尸就归我们
until we're done with it,the corpse is ours.
He is not a corpse.
他不是死尸
He is a mannamed rex van de kamp.
他叫rex van de kamp
He was a loving husband,a devoted father
他是个好丈夫 好父亲
and a successful doctor.
成功的医生
So successful,in fact,that he left me enough money
他太成功了
to sue the city,this precinct
以致他留给我足够的钱 可以控告这个城市 这个管区
and you two gentlemenpersonally
以及在座的二位 只是当为我自己找个乐子
just for the fun of it.
Mrs. Van de kamp,we don'trespond well to threats,
Van de Kamp太太 我们不对威胁做出回应
so if I--release the body.
- 所以我 还他们尸体
What?
什么
The evidence we have is minimal at best.
我们什么证据也没有
Mrs. Van de kampwas gracious enough
Van de Kamp太太主动来这里做测谎试验
to come down hereand take that lie detector test.
I think it's the leastwe can do for her.
这是我们唯一能为她做得
Thank you.
谢谢
So,uh,what will happen now?
那现在该干嘛
Obviously,we'll putmr. Van de kamp back
很显然 我们会把Van de kamp先生放回去 就像我们挖他出土时一样
just like we found him.
Yes,and I'm sureyou will bury him
是啊 而且我确信你们 会像埋死老鼠一样埋了他
with all the dignityof a dead hamster.
No,I want rex released to me
不 把他交给我 我自己来安排
and I will makeall the arrangements.
Fine.
好吧
And,of course,you'll bepaying all the costs.
当然 你们要负责全部开支
Of course.
自然
Detective barton,
Barton警长
you are clearly a gentleman.
你真是个绅士
people have gathered at attenborough high school,
人们聚集在Melanie 曾就读的Attenborough高中
no,it's fine. I'll pick 'em upon my way home.
不 没事的 我回家路上去买
Okay,so what do you want?
好 你要些什么
Oh,parker hates pepperoni.Um,how about sausage?
哦 Parker不吃pepperoni 香肠如何？
Yeah,and a small cheese.
好 还有小奶酪
Okay,perfect. Love you.
好 很好 爱你
Hey,you.
- 嗨宝贝儿
Hey.
- 嗨
You wanna hit o'donnell's?
- 要去O'donnell酒吧么
I owe you a beer.
我欠你一杯酒
Actually,I owe you so much more than that.
事实上我欠你比那可多
You're welcome,but I really need to get home.
不客气 但我真的得回家了
Oh,come on. I had sucha good time last night.
哦 去吧 昨晚我特别开心
Um,why don't you ask trudy?She loves going out.
你找Trudy吧 她爱出去玩
Trudy? Are you kidding?I don't need the competition.
Trudy? 你开玩笑吧？ 我不需要竞争者
Have you seen trudywithout her jacket? She's hot.
你看过Trudy不穿夹克的样子么 特别性感
Oh,is she now?
可不是么
Oh,I-I didn't meanthat you're not... hot.
哦 我不是说你不性感
I just--you're married.
我是说你结婚了
You know,you're off the market.
你已经不约会了 我不用担心跟你争男人
I don't have to worryabout fighting you for guys.
Come on,lynette.Just one quick little drink.
去吧 lynette 就一杯快酒
I was actuallystarting to think
我其实已经觉得我们两个是朋友了
that you and iwere becoming pals.
Pals? 'Cause sometimesit's hard to tell.
朋友？ 有时候还真看不出来
You know,I wasn't feelingthe love today
今天你在客户面前嘲笑我的计划时 我没感觉到多少感情啊
when you mocked my campaignin front of the clients.
That was justputting on a show for work.
我那只是为工作作秀
In the future,always assumethat I am winking inside.
以后 永远想像我内心是在对你挤眼呢
Come on.I hate to go to a bar alone.
好了 我不喜欢自己去酒吧 好像个失败者
I feel like such a loser.
Okay. One drink.
- 好吧 就一杯酒
Yeah! One or two.
- 好 一两杯吧
No.
不
Thank you so much for bringing my mail over.
非常感谢你把我的信送来
You know,I have some of yours in the kitchen.
我厨房还有几封你的信呢
Well,that's the fourth time.What's up with this postman?
这是第四次了 邮递员怎么了
Oh,I know.He used to be great.
哦 是啊 他以前好得很
Then he had this stroke,and,well,
后来他中风了
now we're lucky if hedoesn't drool on the coupons.
现在只要他不在赠券上滴口水 我们就该谢天谢地了
But feel free to snoop around.I'll be right back.
你随意转转吧 我马上回来
now for those of you just joining us,
今天芝加哥的朋友们终于松了口气
families in chicago breathed a sigh of relief today
as an arrest was finally made in the brutal attack
发生在高中生Melanie Foster 身上的残忍袭击 终于抓到了疑犯
on local high school student melanie foster.
But word of the suspect's capture
但疑犯的抓获 对Foster一家 来说算不上什么大的安慰
comes as small comfort
to the foster family...
但疑犯的抓获 对Foster一家 来说算不上什么大的安慰
betty?
Betty？
...Who lost their 17-year-old daughter
他们失去了他们17岁的女儿 大概在4个月前
almost four months ago. Betty?
less than a mile from attenborough high.
受害者的尸体在离attenborough 高中不足一里外的公园发现
Did you see the news?They've arrested somebody.
看新闻了么 他们抓到了一个人
Yeah. Looks likewe're in the clear.
是啊 看来我们没事了
Well,I have some good news.
我有个好消息
The police have finally releasedrex's body.
警方终于放了rex的尸体
About time.
- 是时候了
You must be so relieved.
你可松了口气了
You know,mostly I'm just annoyed
知道么 我打一开始对
that the whole thing happened in the first place.
这件事本身就烦透了
I mean,how in the world could anybody accuse me of murder?
这世界上怎么会有人怀疑我杀人
Well,you are wound pretty tight.
你总是井井有条的样子
What? The supermom is always the first to snap.
怎么了 模范母亲最容易崩溃
They've done studies.
调查显示如此
Anyway,I was hoping
总之 我希望你们周五早上都能有空
that you were all freefriday morning,
because that's when I'm goingto be hosting the reburial.
因为我要在那时候重新举办葬礼
The what?
什么
Look,I know it's an imposition,
我也知道这有点不妥 但Danielle跟班级野营去了
but danielle is awayon a class trip,
and andrew is backat camp hennessey
Andrew在Hennessey营地参加复训课程
for a little refresher course.
Well,it's just gonna be
这只会是一个很简短庄严的仪式
a very briefand dignified ceremony,
and I was hoping thatyou could say a few words,
我期望你们当时都能说几句
and,um,I'm gonna read a poem.
而我会读一首诗
We would love to come.
- 我们很愿意参加
Absolutely.
没问题
I'm busy. Sorry.
我没空 不好意思
(Whispers) edie!
Edie!
(Whispers)she's going to read a poem.
她要读诗！
Fine. Yes,yes,we'd all love to come.
好！没问题 我们都愿意参加
Well,thank you.
谢谢大家
You don't know how muchthis means to me.
我真的感激不尽
I realize looking backthat I was still in shock
我现在回想 意识到在rex的第一次葬礼 我还处在震惊之中
during rex's first funeral.
I don't think it had quitehit me yet what had happened,
当时我没有意识到到底发生了什么
so that's why this smallceremony means so much to me,
当时我没有意识到到底发生了什么 这就是为什么这次小仪式对我这么重要
because I realize now that...
因为我现在意识到了
this is the last chanceI'm gonna have to say good-bye.
这是我最后一次说再见的机会
Unless,of course,they dig him up again.
除非他们再把他挖出来
Sure,there was times when
的确 有时候Lisa会很粗鲁很讨厌
lisa was rude and obnoxious,
but I know now thatthat was no excuse
但我现在明白这不能构成我打她的借口
to always be beatin' on her.
Oh,baby,I'm so sorry.
哦 宝贝 对不起
Good job,you two.
很好 你们两个
This is an example of how to useincarceration to your benefit.
这就是怎么利用好入狱时光的例子
It's a chance for peopleto take a step back
这是后退一步的机会
and observe the obstaclesthey face in their marriage.
来观察他们婚姻中出现的障碍
Can I go now?'Cause I have a lot to say
我现在能说了么 因为我有很多关于我婚姻的障碍要说
about the obstacles I'm facing in my marriage.
因为我有很多关于我婚姻的障碍要说
We don't got any obstacles.
- 我们没有障碍
Yes,we do,lamar.
We got big ones.
我们有 Lamar 很大的障碍
Okay,hold on,you two.
好了 稍等 二位
I think that it'scarlos and gabrielle's turn.
我想现在轮到Carlos和gabrielle了
Thanks,but we're good.
谢谢 但不用了
this is your third group session,
这是你们第三次来了
but you have yet to share anything.
但你们还什么也没说过
Come on. Talk to us.How's your marriage?
来 跟我们说说 你们的婚姻状况
Shaky at best.And why is that?
为什么会这样呢
I don't know.I hired a brilliant lawyer
不知道 我请了一位高明的律师
to get my husband out of this hellhole,
来帮我丈夫脱离这个地狱
and he fired him for no reason at all.
他却没缘故的炒了人家
Carlos?
carlos说说
I just didn't like him.
- 我就是不喜欢他
Why not?
- 为什么不
He's experienced,he's intelligent,
他有经验 有智慧
he's successful.
他很成功
Exactly. I'd prefer an attorney you didn't find so damn appealing.
说得对 我更想要个不怎么让你着迷的律师
Oh,my god. You fired him because you're jealous?
哦 天哪 你因为嫉妒解雇了他？
Don't I have the right to?
我没权力嫉妒么
You know,she cheated on me.
你们知道 她有过外遇
oh,bob,you beat your wife.
哦 Bob 你还打你老婆呢
You are so not allowed to gasp.
- 你有什么权力喘粗气
Don't you talk that wayto him.
别那样跟他说话
One more word out of you,lisa,and I will backhand you myself.
再多一句嘴 Lisa 我亲自收拾你
Okay,calm down.
- 好了 冷静点
Thousands of fat,bald attorneys out there in the world,
到处是又肥又秃的律师
and she's gotta get the one that looks like an underwear model.
- 她却找了个跟内衣模特似的
I'm not discussing this anymore.
我不管了
You can rot in here for all I care.
你在这鬼地方烂死吧
So,um...
那么
mona,what do you feel
Mona 你觉得
are the biggest problem sin your marriage?
你们婚姻最大的问题在哪呢
By the way,he was wearing a suit.
另外 他穿着西装
How do you know he had a good body?
你怎么知道他身材好呢
Do you know?
- 那你知道么?
No!
不知道！
I bet he's hot.
我猜他肯定特性感
Do I need to say whatour biggest problem is,
我还用说我们的最大问题么
or can everybody figure it outfor themselves?
还是大家都自己看出来了
Why are you readingthat contract?
你读这份合同干嘛
I told you. Lonny wants meto sign with this new agency.
我跟你说了 Lonny想让我和这个新公司签约
But you didn't say
但你没说你在认真考虑跟他工作
you were seriously thinkingabout going with him.
I know,I know.
我明白 明白
Just lonny's family.
Lonny像家人一样
You know,he's alwaysbeen there for me.
在我等待第一张版税支票的时候
He paid my rentwhen I was waiting
是他给我付的房租 Karl离开我的时候 是他每天都打电话安慰我
for my first royalty check.
Karl离开我的时候 是他每天都打电话安慰我
He called me every daywhen karl left.
I mean,I just owe himso much.
我欠他太多了
Susan,he committed a felony.
Susan 他犯了重罪
Okay,who in this room
好吧 这屋子谁没犯过重罪 举起手来
has not committed a felony?Raise your hand.
Ah-ah-ah,not so fast.
啊~ 你再好好想想
Your agent represents you.
你的经纪人代表你
You've gotta be ableto trust him.
你一定要能信任他 现在你还能做的到么
How is that gonna bepossible now?
Well,it's possible becauseI have faith in people.
能做到 因为我相信人
I mean,lonny knowshe messed up,
Lonny知道他犯错了 他很后悔 他正在还债呢
and he's sorry.He's making restitution.
What,you don't believe peopledeserve second chances?
怎么 你不觉得该给人第二次机会么
Not when they messed upthis much,no.
犯了这么大的错就不该
Really? So that's it with you?You just get one shot,
是么 你真这样么 你就给人一次机会 人家搞砸了 就此完蛋？
and you screw up,and you're out?
I didn't knowyou were such a cynic.
不知道你这么愤世嫉俗
Hey,I'm sorry,all right?
不知道你这么愤世嫉俗 对不起 好么 我想我就是这么个人
I guess it's justthe way I'm wired.
对不起 好么 我想我就是这么个人
I got a jobover in greenwood,
我在Greenwood有个活儿
so I'll call youlater tonight.
今天晚点给你打电话
You okay?
你还好吧
julie...
Julie
I did something bad,something really,really bad.
我做了件坏事 天大的坏事
Last week when mike and iwent to the park
上周我跟Mike去公园找zach
searching for zach,
Yes,and I gave him moneyand I sent him away,
真的 我给了他钱把他送走了
and I didn't tell mike.
我没告诉Mike
See,this would neverhappen to me.
我可办不出这样的事 就你能办得出来
This kind of thingonly happens to you.
Will you stop judgingand help me?
你能停止批判来帮帮我么
You heard what he saidabout his wiring.
你也听他说了他是什么样的人
I betrayed him.
我背叛了他 他永远不会原谅我的
I can barely look him in the eyewhen he talks about zach.
他说zach的时候我都不敢看他眼睛
So where do you thinkzach went?
你认为Zach去哪了
Utah.
犹他州
Oh,lord.Why did I do this?
哦 上帝 我为什么要那样做
I have a feelingyou did it for me.
我猜你是为了我
Hey,girl. I hope you arein the mood for margaritas
我希望你有来点margarita的情绪
'cause it is salsa nightat o'donnell'S.
因为今晚O'donnell是Salsa之夜
Oh,fun. But I can't go tonightbecause I promised the twins
哦 不赖 但我今晚不能去
that I would help themfinish their science project.
我答应双胞胎们帮他们完成科技手工
Lynette,if the late hours
Lynette 要是加班对你来说有困难
are going to be an issuefor you,
we probably shouldtalk about finding you
我们或许该给你找个清闲点的活儿干
a less demanding account.
You're gonnatake me off kamarov
你要我不再做kamarov
because I won't godrinking with you?
只因为我不肯陪你去喝酒?
No. Oh,god,no.
不 哦,天哪，不是的 亲爱的,我知道你有家庭
Honey,I get it.You have a family.
I mean,for me,the client comes first.
我是说,对我来说 客户才是第一位的
Me being a perfectionistis my own neurotic issue,
为此我神经质似地把个人的事情处理好 而且我也知道我真的需要你来做那事情
and I know that I reallyneed to work on that.
But trust me,I will never sleep again
但相信我,要是这个案子给弄砸了 我就再也不会睡觉了
if this campaign getsmucked up.
I'll figure something out.You go home. Have a good night.
我会想清楚的你回家 晚上过的愉快
Nina?
Yeah.
什么
I can handle the extra hours.
我能处理额外的时间
Oh,lynette. You sure?
哦,lynette你确定?
Yeah.
对
I'll get my coat.
我去拿外套
Wow,this place is rowdyafter happy hour,huh?
哦,这地方欢乐时光很吵啊,啊?
Yeah.
对
Hey... look at that guyright there.
嘿 看看那里的那个人 吧台最后的
The end of the bar.
The shoulderswith the tan jacket.
肩膀上披着棕褐色夹克的
Yeah.
看到了
Go get him for me.
把他给我叫来
hey there.
嘿，那儿的人
So they're going on aboutmelanie foster on the news.
他们在新闻里报道了melanie foster
It's time we talked about her,caleb.
是时候我们来谈谈她了,caleb
Until you start acceptingresponsibility
在你为发生了的事情重新负起责之前
for what happened,
you know I can't let youout of here.
你知道我是不能让你出去的
What the hell is this?!Mom!
这是该死的什么?!妈妈!
where are you?!
你在哪里?!
I'll be right back.
我马上就回来
And I will expect youto answer me.
希望你能回答我
where are you?!
你在哪里?!
I'm coming! Coming.
我来了! 来了
"I know who really killedmelanie foster.
"我知道谁是真的杀了 melanie foster的凶手
"You've arrestedthe wrong man"?
"你们抓错人了"? 你到底在想什么?
What are you thinking?
We are good people.
我们是好人
Well,then call 9-1-1and tell 'em
那么,就打给9-1-1然后告诉他们 你把一个杀人凶手关在地下室里
you got a killerlocked up in the basement.
He is not a killer.He was confused.
他不是杀人凶手 他只是有点混乱
He didn't knowwhat he was doing.
他都不知道他在干什么
He knows a lot more thanyou give him credit for.
他比你给他的信任要知道的多
Mom,are youthinking it through?
妈妈，你想过吗?
I'm mailing the letter.
我会把信寄出去的
If you do,you'd better hopeto god they don't find us.
如果你做了 你最好向上帝祈祷他们不会找上我们
'Cause they're not gonna carehow slow caleb is.
因为他们不会在意caleb反应有多慢
They'll just execute him.
他们只会处死他
Are you here? It's susan.
在吗? 是susan
Lonny?
在吗? 是susan Lonny?
Susan?
What are you doing here?
你在这里干吗?
Well,I just came overto give you the contracts.
我是来给你这份合约的
Your door was open.
你的门开着
Oh. Great.
哦很好
Sorry this placeis such a mess.
抱歉，这里太乱了。
I've been working here tillwe get the new offices painted.
我会在这里工作直到 我们把办公室全漆好
Wait till you see them.
等着看啊 会非常非常漂亮的
They're gonna bereally beautiful.
Where's jeannie?
jeannie在哪里?
She's with the kidsup in minnesota
他和孩子们去明尼苏达州了去看她母亲 她们很喜欢那里
visiting her mom.
They love it up there.
他和孩子们去明尼苏达州了去看她母亲 她们很喜欢那里
Keep changing the dateon dear old dad.
得根据老法算日子
Oh,I'm such a dummy.
哦,你瞧我这人
I've been...
我曾经
I've been so swamped,
我记不得了 大概是忘了付电费了
I must have forgottento pay the electric bill.
Lonny...
Lonny
how much financial troubleare you really in?
你财务上到底有多困难?
I'm fine.
我很好
You know what it is?
你知道吗?
I had to pay all those peopleback at the same time--
我要同时付所有那些人的钱 偿还加利息
restitution plus interest.
It's not somethingI'd recommend.
我可不推荐这样做 那都把你榨干了
It sucks you dry.
I've gonna ask youa question,
我要问你个问题 并且要你说实话
and I want youto tell me the truth.
Please don't lie.Just tell me.
别说谎说实话
Is that what you wantto hear?
那是你想要听的吗?
Do I have to say itso that we can move on?
是不是非要我承认了我们才能继续下去?
Fine. I did it.
那好吧 我偷了
But yours wasthe first money I paid back,
但你的会是我最先还的 那石板就能早点被铺好
so the slate'sbeen wiped clean.
Let's just move past it.
就让我们忘了那些吧
Suze?
I'm sorry. I just can'ttrust you anymore.
对不起我只是不能再信任你了
You can.Can'T.
你可以说不能
okay,okay,fine.
好吧,好吧,好吧
Aah! What are you doing?!
啊! 你在干吗?!
Are you tryingto take me down with you?!
你想把我一起拖下水吗?!
I am not going down!
我不会下去的
My life is great!
我的生活很好!
I have never been happier,
从没那么开心过 也从没那么瘦过!
and I've never been thinner!
Get off me,you amazon!
放开我,你疯了!
what are you doing here?
你在这里干吗?
You left me a message.You said you wanted to talk.
你留了张条子你说你想谈谈
Yeah,I thought you'd schedulean appointment later.
对,我以为你会再安排一次会面
Right now I'm sort ofdisgusting and sweaty.
现在我可又不中看又浑身是汗
I'm a criminal lawyer.I've seen worse.
我是个犯罪律师见过更糟的
So did you find a new lawyerfor mr. Charming?
那么你给迷人先生找到别的律师了吗?
I don't want a new lawyer.I want you.
我不想要别的律师我就想要你
So does carlos.He just doesn't realize it yet.
而carlos他只是还没意识到
A 1988 romane-conti la tche.I'm impressed.
A 1988 roman-conti la tche 我印象深刻
Look,to be honest,carlos isa little threatened by you.
听着,说实话,carlos有点被你吓到
He thinks if we spendtoo much time together,
他认为我们要是在一起时间长了 会有点
that something...might happen.
他认为我们要是在一起时间长了 会有点 会有点那个
Somebody's gotan active imagination.
有些人的想像力就是丰富
Corkscrew?
螺丝锥有吗?
David,we're not hereto drink wine,okay?
David,我们在一起不是喝酒的,好吗?
This is business.
这是生意
Now you have to convincecarlos that he can trust you.
你现在要说服carlos让他相信你
How am I gonna do that?
我要怎么才能做到呢?
I don't know. Tell him you'rehappily married or--or gay.
我不知道 告诉他你婚姻幸福--或者是个同性恋
yeah,right.
好,好
You're a lawyer. You lieto juries all the time.
你是个律师 你一直都要对陪审团撒谎的
Can't you just make something up?
你就不能稍做点什么吗?
I'm past the pointin my career
为了份工作这种事情 我已经做的够多的了抱歉
where I have to beg for work.I'm sorry.
Okay,david,I'm holdingmy marriage together
好吧,david,我的婚姻就在此一搏了
by my fingernails.
If carlos serveshis full sentence,
如果carlos要服完整个刑期 我想我们就很难继续我们的婚姻了
I don't think we're gonnamake it,so please,I need you.
所以求你了,我需要你
I'll say this much for carlos.He's got excellent taste...
我要说这完全是为了carlos 他品位非常好
in wine. Montrachet.It's good stuff.
关于酒 关于Montrachet 那可是个好东西
Are you gonna help meor not?
你到底要不要帮我?
We'll go see carlos tomorrow.I'll turn him around for you.
我们明天去见carlos 我会帮你把他要回来的
Really?What are you gonna say?
真的吗?你打算怎么说?
Play it by ear. I don't wannasound too over-rehearsed.
看情况 我不想让人看起来像是过分排练过的
Hey,that's my wine.
嘿,那是我的酒
Deduct it from my bill.
从我的帐单上扣
It all started withbad real estate investments.
全都是因为糟糕的房产投资开始的
You should have justcome clean.
你只要做清白就行了
Yeah,well,you tell one lie,the second one comes easy.
是啊,当你说了一个谎 第二个就接踵而来
Then you're making up new liesto cover up the old ones.
然后你就要用新的谎言去弥补旧的
Pretty soon,you can't turn back,you know?
非常快,你就回不了头了,知道吗?
I do.
知道
When jeannie finally caught on,she took the kids.
当jeannie终于知道了的时候 她带走了孩子
She took the furniture.
带走了家具
The bank locked meout of my own house.
银行把我锁在我自己家门外
That's why I can't lose youas a client.
这就是我不能失去你这个客户的原因
Well,I'm sorry,but you have.
那么,很抱歉,你还是失去了
I don't blame you.
我不怪你
You'll never lose my friendship,though.
但你永远不会失去我的友情的
I mean that.
- 我是认真的
真的吗？
真的吗?
Of course.You're my lonny.
当然你是我的lonny
and you're my susie.
而你是我的susie
you're my susie.
你是我的susie
Oh! What the hellis wrong with you?!
哦!你这是怎么回事?!
I'm your lonny.That's what you said.
我是你的lonny 你刚刚这么说的
I mean,there's alwaysbeen this magnetism.
我是说,这种吸引力常常是存在的
No,there has not been,and there never will be!
不,不存在,也永远不会存在!
Oh,my god!
我的上帝啊!
But I was just coming clean!
可我正要变的清白!
Hey,morgan!
嘿,morgan!
Got a letterfrom some guy
有人写信来说他袭击了melanie foster
claiming he attackedmelanie foster.
You ran me down for that?
你要我做那个?
I got dozens of kooks coming out of the woodwork,
我这里有一打疯子从woodwork来
all saying we arrested the wrong guy.
嚷着说我抓错了人
This one knows about the ax.
这个家伙知道斧头的事情
Here you go,mrs. Van de kamp.
来了,Van de kamp太太
Thank you.The hearse is right outside,
谢谢灵车就在外面
so if you'll just follow me...
所以你只要跟着我走就行了
oh,shoot. There's a formI need you to sign.
哦,等等 还有份表格要您填一下
I think I left it back in the office.
我想我是把它忘在办公室里了
That's all right.
- 没关系
I'll wait.Okay.
-  我可以等
I'm here,sweetheart,
我在这里,亲爱的,
and I'm gonna take careof everything.
我会照顾一切的
But you knew that,didn't you?
可你都知道的,对吗? 你一直都知道我是你能依靠的
You've always knownthat you can count on me.
Mrs. Van de kamp.
Van de kamp太太
Detective barton,what are you doing here?
barton侦探,你在这里干吗?
Oh,just taking careof some business.
哦,有点公事要办
Is this...
这是
yes. This is rex.
对是rex
I-I wanna thank you againfor what you did.
我，我想再次为你做的事情谢谢你
It was so refreshingto be treated with kindness
在经历了那么多日子荒唐的责难后 能被那么客气的对待真是太好了
after weeks of justludicrous accusations.
The doctor doesn't thinkthey're ludicrous.
医生可不认为那是荒唐的
Well,I know,but rex died in his care.
我知道,可rex是在他的照顾下死的呀
I mean,of course he'd liketo blame someone else.
我是说,他当然想要找个别人来负责了
Rex was not poisoned,
Rex没被下毒 而且我认识的人里没有相信这个的
and no one I know believes that he was.
Rex did.
- Rex相信
Well,the doctor told rexhe was being poisoned,
医生告诉rex他被下下毒 而rex相信了他
and rex believed him.
How would you know that?
你怎么知道的?
Oh!
Where did you get this?
这从哪里来的?
We found that in rex's bedafter he died.
我们在rex死后在他的床头柜找到的 那是他的笔迹,是吗?
That is his handwriting,isn't it?
You know what I think?
你知道我怎么想的吗?
Rex felt guiltyfor the way he treated you.
Rex为他对待你的方式而感到有罪
The adultery,the public humiliations.
通奸,在公众面前的耻辱
That's why he forgave you.He understood why you did it.
那就是他原谅你的原因 他明白你这么做的原因
How couldhe have believed this?
他怎么会相信这个?
Look,my wife cheated on me,too.
听着,我太太也欺骗了我 我知道那有多受伤
I know how much it hurts.
And so will a judge.
也知道一个判断有多伤人 人人都相信因一时激动而犯罪
Everyone understandscrimes of passion.
But every daythat you stonewall
可每一天当你小心翼翼地过着 却让你看起来越来越冷
makes you lookmore and more
like a cold,calculating killer.
就像有预谋的杀人犯
We both knowthat's not you.
我们都知道那不是你
But I can't help you unlessyou start telling the truth.
但在你说真话前我帮不了你
I'm sorry,but I-I,um,I have to go.
对不起,可我-我,恩,我要走了
I have some thingsthat I need to take care of.
我有些事情要去办
Bree,it is obvious your husbandloved you very much.
Bree,很明显你丈夫非常爱你
Don't you think you owe to himto admit the truth?
你难道不认为你欠他这个真相吗?
Detective,I know exactlywhat my husband deserves.
侦探,我很清楚我丈夫到底要的是什么 你来帮个忙好吗?
Now would you be a dear?
Thank you.
谢谢
What's he doing here?
他到这里来干吗?
I have a pitch for you.
我给你找了个出路
I wanna explain to you
我想解释给你听为什么 我认为你会对允许我来尊重你感兴趣
why I think it's in your bestinterest for you to allow me
to represent you.
我想解释给你听为什么 我认为你会对允许我来尊重你感兴趣
Oh,for pete's sake,carlos,at least listen to the man.
哦,看在上帝的份上,carlos 你至少听他要说什么
I guess it beatssitting in my cell.
我猜是我的细胞作祟
Now I don't think you havea problem with me as a lawyer.
现在我知道我作为律师 你和我没什么问题
Clearly,I'm the real deal.
很明显,我公事公办
I sense your problemwith me is more personal.
我感觉你和我的问题是因为私人原因
You sense right.
你的感觉没错
You wanna know if I'm interestedin sleeping with your wife.
你想知道我有没有兴趣和你太太上床
And the answer is yes.
答案是我有
he--carlos,he's kidding.
他--carlos,他在开玩笑
tell him you're kidding.
- 告诉他你在开玩笑
Shut it.
- 闭嘴
Now clearly,
现在清楚了,gabrielle是任性的 自我为中心并且很有心计
gabrielle's willful,self-centered and manipulative.
She's also beautiful enoughto be worth the trouble.
她也漂亮的足够抵消这些麻烦了
So the minutewe leave this room,
所以当我们离开这间房间时 我会积极地追着她
I'm going to aggressivelypursue her,
and when I succeed,which I will,
当我成功时,我会成功的
we're gonna flyto my chateau in chamonix
我们会飞到我在沙木尼的城堡去 然后在当地的小酒馆吃饭
and have dinnerin a local bistro.
They make the best raclettein all of europe.
他们做全欧洲最好的raclettein
We'll make love by the fireand afterwards
我们会在炉火边做爱 然后在半夜滑会儿雪
do a little midnight skiing.You ski,don't you?
我们会在炉火边做爱 然后在半夜滑会儿雪 你滑雪的吧?
You're athletic.You'll learn.
你像个运动员你可以学
Anyway,all of thisonly happens if you fire me.
总之,这些都只会在你解雇我之后发生
If you keep me onas your lawyer,
如果你把我当作你的律师 你太太就很安全
your wife's off-limits.
I'd get disbarred for sleepingwith a client's wife,
因和客户的妻子有染而被取消执照 没人值得我那么做,她也不值得
and nobody's worth that,not even her.
So that's my pitch.
这就是我的建议
I'll let you think about it.
我会让你好好考虑的
Honey,I am so sorry.
亲爱的,我很抱歉
Honestly,that guy's insane.
说真的,那个家伙很疯狂
Boy,you just can't wait,can you?
你就是等不了,是吧?
What?
什么?
He's my lawyer.But,carlos--
他当我的律师
and that's allthere is to it.
- 可,carlos-- 就这样了
How about a dance?
- 跳支舞怎么样?
How about it?
怎么样?
Yes.
好啊
Well,you guys have fun.
那么,玩的高兴点
This is the fifth nightin a row
这是连轴转的第五天了 我都没有回家替孩子盖过被子
I haven't been hometo tuck in my kids,
so I'm gonna go.
- 所以我要走了
No. You're gonna stay put.
不 你要留下
It is friday night, and you have all weekend to play with your kids.
这是星期五晚上 你有整个周末和你的孩子们玩
Watch my purse.
看着我的包
I'm chuck.
我是chuck
Chuck,I'm gonna stop youright there.
Chuck,我要你现在就停下
Happily married.
婚姻幸福。
Well...
那么
looks like we have gotsomething in common.
看起来我们有共同之处啊
Ugh.
Chuck?
Get your handoff my thigh.
把你的手从我腿上拿开
No,not up my thigh.Off it.
不,不是要放我腿上拿开
Come on!What's the matter with you?
快点!你怎么了?
I'm not available.And I'm not that easy!
我不需要别人而且我也没那么容易得到!
Well,what are you doing ina pick-up bar at 10:30 at night?
那么,那你晚上10点半 在这么个酒吧你干吗?
Well,I don't usuallydo this.
其实我不常这样
Oh,come on,honey,who are you kidding?
哦,来吧,宝贝,你在和谁开玩笑?
I've seen you here every nightthis week. You're a regular.
我这星期每天都在这里看到你 你是个常客
At that moment it occurred to lynette
在那一刻，对lynette而言 那个chuck,尽管醉了
that chuck,though inebriated,
had a valid point.
却有个正确的观点
The time had come to declare
时间到了该为独立而战的时候了
a war of independence.
And the surest path to victory
而通往胜利的道路
would require an aggressive campaign
需要具震动意义的
of shock...
积极的活动
and awe.
还有敬畏
it's crazy here tonight.
今晚这里太疯狂了
Don't you wantto dance?
你不想跳舞吗?
No,thanks. I thinkI'll sit this one out.
不,谢了 我想就坐坐吧
Lynette savored her victory
Lynette体会着她的胜利，自信
confident that she would never again
Lynette体会着她的胜利，自信 她再也不会为这场特别的 战争中的对手了所累了
have to engage her opponent on this particular battlefield.
她再也不会为这场特别的 战争中的对手了所累了
Ooh! I love this song.
哦! 我爱这首歌 给你,看着我的包
Here,hold my purse.
Bree,where have you been?We were starting to get worried.
Bree,你去哪里了?我们都开始担心你了
Oh,I'm sorry.
哦,很抱歉 我只是为最后一点小细节而耽搁了点
I was just attendingto some last minute details.
Right this way.Where are we going?
这里走
To rex's gravesite.
- 到rex的墓地去
Well,I thought that this was his grave site.
可我以为这里就是他的墓地
Well,he did something toupset me,and I want him gone.
他做了让我难过的事情 所以我要他离开
What did he do?
他做了什么?
You know,it's so unpleasant.I'd rather not get into it.
你知道吗,那太让我伤心了 我宁可不再提了
Have you seen these gravestones?Some are from the 1800s.
看到那些幕石了吗? 有些从19世纪就有了
Rex is dead. What couldhe have done to upset you?
Rex死了他能做的了什么来让你生气的?
My husband,the man I spentmy life with for 18 years,
我的丈夫,这个和我一起 度过了18年人生的男人
died thinking that I murdered him.
- 死的时候竟然认为是我杀了他
What?
- 什么?
Yes,the cardiologist shared this moronic theory with rex.
而且那个心脏病专家和 rex说了这种愚蠢的理论
And rex believed him!
- 而rex竟然相信他!
Are you sure?
你肯定吗?
Yes,because he left a note and it said,and I quote,
当然,因为他留了张字条说了 我记下来的
"bree,I understand.And I forgive you."
"bree,我理解你我也原谅你"
I spent 18 years of my lifewith this man.
我和这个男人一起度过了18年的人生
How could he not know me?
他怎么能那么不懂我?
Well,maybe he was forgiving youfor something else.
也许他是为了什么别的事情原谅你
I have done nothing to be forgiven for!
我没做什么需要他原谅的事情!
I was a fantastic wife!
我是一个非常出色的妻子!
When he was sick,I nursed him.
他病了的时候,我照顾他
When we were low on money,I stayed within a budget.
当我们缺钱的时候,我尽心量入为出
I cooked his meals.I mended his clothes.
我为他做饭我为他改衣服
For the love of god,I usedto check his back for acne.
看在上帝的份上 我还为他查看过他背上的粉刺
And that miserableson of a bitch
而那个可悲的狗娘养的 却有空来原谅我?
has the nerve to understandand forgive me?
because I do not understand,and I do not forgive.
现在，好笑的是他 因为我不理解他,也不原谅他
Hi. We're--we're just going to a funeral.
嗨 我们--我们正要去葬礼
Right this way.
这边走
Honey,I know you're hurt,but are you sure
亲爱的,我知道这伤害了你 但你确定你不会改变主意了吗?
you're not gonnachange your mind?
I mean,there's noturning back after this.
我是说,这可没有回头路走
If you think I'm gonnalay next to someone for eternity
如果你认为我会葬在那个 误解我的人旁边，你肯定是疯了
who thinks I'm a murderer,you're crazy.
As far as I'm concerned,
可我所担心的是,
let him decomposewith strangers.
让他和陌生人一起腐烂
Everyone in the world needs someone they can depend on,
这个世界上的每个人都需要有人依靠,
be they faithful friends,
作最忠诚的朋友,
determined advocates...
一起做决定
or a loving family.
或组成温暖的家庭
But occasionally in life,
可有时生活里,
the people we thought would always be there for us leave.
那个我们认为一直会在那里 让我们依靠的人也会离开
And if that happens,
当它发生时,
it's amazing the lengths we'll go to...
去把他们再找回来的路
to get them back.
异常的艰难
Sync:YTET-fisherchen
欲乱绝情妻 第二季 第05集
=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
=结束=-